https://preisner.com/privacy-policy

The official website of
Zbigniew Preisner
Privacy policy
1. General Terms
1) preisner.com and any associated companies or third parties are committed to protecting you and your family’s personal information when you are using preisner.com. We want our services to be safe and enjoyable environments for our audience. This Privacy Policy relates to our use of any personal information you provide to us through preisner.com.
2) The Website is operated by Preisner Productions (we, us, our) a company incorporated in Poland. Where we decide the purpose or means for the processing of the personal data that you provide when using our Website, we are the “data controller” for the purposes of the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR). This policy should be read together with our Terms & Conditions of the Website.
3) Our Website may contain hyperlinks to third party websites. These websites operate fully independently from us, and we cannot accept any responsibility or liability for the privacy practices of such third parties nor the availability of these external sites or resources. The appearance of such links on our Website is not an endorsement. Should you use any of these websites, such use is at your own risk and we would recommend that you review their respective privacy policies.
2. Usage of your personal data
1) Your Enquiries
If you contact us about our services, the forms you complete or the emails you send may include information about you, such as your name as the contact point for an organisation, your email address, the organisation's address and your enquiry. We use this information to respond to your enquiries.
In line with the legitimate interest we have in promoting our business, we will process your enquiries to reply and provide you with information about the services we offer.
We may also process enquiries to take steps you ask of us with a view to entering into an agreement to provide you with our services.
You are under no obligation to provide us with any details, but if you don’t provide all relevant information, we may not be able to help.
2) Website (Analytics)
Our Website uses cookies and other mechanisms, such as third party pixels and Google Tag manager, to collect analytical information, such as your internet protocol (IP) address, to help analyse how visitors use the Website.
We process this information to understand how visitors use our Website and to compile statistical reports regarding that activity (for example, your IP address is used to approximate the country from which you access our Website, and we aggregate this information together so we know that, for example, that visitors to our Website come from a specific territory). This information is not used by us to develop a personal profile of you.
We or other companies may use cookies to suggest and deliver content which we believe may interest you. Some of our webpages may use plug-ins from other organisations (such as Google, Facebook and Spotify). These other organisations may use information about your visit to our Websites on their pages. For more information on how these organisations use information, please read their privacy policies.
This processing is necessary for us to pursue our legitimate interests in improving our Website, and providing a better service and source of information to visitors.
You can always choose to enable or disable Cookies in your internet browser. By default, most internet browsers accept Cookies but this can be changed.
Google Analytics : We may use Google Analytics on our Website for anonymous reporting of Website usage If you would like to opt- out of Google Analytics monitoring your behaviour on our Website please use this link (https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/ )
3) Content you submit to us
If you send us objectionable content or otherwise behave in a disruptive manner when using our Website, we may process personal data included in your messages to respond to and stop such behaviour.
We only process personal data in this way for the legitimate interests of ensuring that use of our Website is lawful, does not disrupt our systems, does not harass our staff or other individuals, and to enforce our legal rights and to comply with our legal obligations.
Where we reasonably believe you are or may be in breach of the law (for instance, because content you send amounts to harassment or is defamatory), we may use your personal information to inform relevant third parties such as your email/internet provider or law enforcement agencies about the content.
Where we process personal data in this way, we will hold that personal information on our systems for as long as is reasonably necessary to achieve these objectives.
4) Purchases
We do not offer any direct sales via our Website. Any purchases you make on the websites listed below are operated by third parties and subject to their terms and conditions and privacy policy. We recommend that you review these.
3. Sharing informations
We keep your information confidential, but may disclose it to our personnel, suppliers or subcontractors insofar as it is reasonably necessary for the purposes set out in this privacy policy, provided that they do not make independent use of the information.
We only permit them to process your personal data for specified purposes and in accordance with our instructions. All our third party service providers are required to take appropriate security measures to protect your personal information in line with our policies. Activities which are carried out by third party service providers include: CRM management software, website hosting, and IT support.
Sharing
In addition, we may disclose your information to the extent that we are required to do so by law (which may include to government bodies and law enforcement agencies); in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings; and to establish, exercise or defend our legal rights (including providing information to others for the purposes of fraud prevention).
If we are involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of our business or assets, the information we hold may be included as part of that sale, in which case you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on the Website of any changes in ownership or use of your information, as well as any choices you may have regarding that information.
Except as provided above, we will not provide your information to third parties.
4. Your rights in relation to personal data
You have the following rights over the way we process personal data relating to you. We aim to comply without undue delay in response to any requests by you:
for a copy of data we are processing about you and have inaccuracies corrected;
to restrict, stop processing, or to delete your personal data;
for a machine readable copy of your personal data, which you can use with another service provider. Where it is technically feasible, you can ask us to send this information directly to another provider if you prefer; and
to make a complaint to a data protection regulator. Please send your requests to
5. Children
We do not use the Website to knowingly solicit data from or market to children under the age of 13. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with information without their consent, he or she should contact us at preisnerproductions@gmail.com. We will delete such information within a reasonable time.
6. Security
We will take all reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss misuse or alteration of your personal information.
7. Changes to policy
This policy may be updated from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new policy here and, where feasible, by letting you know by email.
8. International Data Transfers
Some information we hold may be stored on servers that may be located outside of the European Economic Area (EEA). With certain service providers, we may use specific contracts approved by the European Commission which give personal data the same protection it has in Europe.
Where we use providers based in the US, we may transfer data to them if they are part of the Privacy Shield which requires them to provide similar protection to personal data shared between the Europe and the US.
If you would like to find out more about these safeguards, please let us know by writing to preisnerproductions@gmail.com
9. Retention Periods
We will hold your personal information on our systems for as long as is necessary for the relevant purpose, or as otherwise described in this privacy policy.
To determine the appropriate retention period for personal data, we consider the amount, nature, and sensitivity of the personal data, the potential risk of harm from unauthorised use or disclosure of your personal data, the purposes for which we process your personal data and whether we can achieve those purposes through other means, and the applicable legal requirements.
This site uses cookies according to
Privacy Policy. You can specify the conditions for storing or accessing cookies in your browser.
